To write unit and integration tests,
Para escribir pruebas de unidad e integracin, necesita
you need a testing framework. There are several testing frameworks
un marco de prueba. Existen varios frameworks de
out there but the most popular ones are: NUnit:
prueba, pero los ms populares son: NUnit: que es
which is one of the earliest frameworks out there, we've got MSTest,
uno de los frameworks ms antiguos, tenemos MSTest, que
which is Microsoft's testing framework built into
es el marco de prueba de Microsoft integrado en
Visual Studio, and Xunit, which has gained more
Visual Studio, y Xunit, que ha ganado ms popularidad.
popularity over the past couple of years. All these frameworks
en los ltimos aos. Todos estos marcos le brindan una
give you a utility library to write your tests and a test
biblioteca de utilidad para escribir sus pruebas y un corredor de prueba
runner which runs your tests and gives you a report of
que ejecuta sus pruebas y le brinda un informe de las pruebas
passing and failing tests. Which framework is better? It depends
de aprobacin y falla. Qu marco es mejor? Depende de a quin le
who you ask and what their definition of better is. Different people
pregunte y cul es su definicin de mejor. A diferentes personas les
like different tools. So, here is my suggestion: Don't get hung up on the tooling.
gustan diferentes herramientas. Por lo tanto, aqu est mi sugerencia: No te cuelgues de las herramientas.
In this course, our focus is on the fundamentals
En este curso, nuestro enfoque se centra en los fundamentos de redaccin de
of writing quality tests that give you value. That's what
pruebas de calidad que le dan valor. Eso es
matters. You can always use a different framework as you move from one
lo que importa. Siempre puede usar un marco diferente a medida
project or team to another. In this course, you're going to start
que pasa de un proyecto o equipo a otro. En este curso, vas a
with MSTest because that's built into Visual Studio
comenzar con MSTest porque est integrado en Visual Studio y
and doesn't require any additional steps. But shortly after,
no requiere ningn paso adicional. Pero poco despus, le
I'm gonna show you how to install NUnit and run NUnit tests
mostrar cmo instalar NUnit y ejecutar pruebas de
in Visual Studio. You may use either of these frameworks, that's
NUnit en Visual Studio. Puede usar cualquiera de estos marcos,
purely your personal decision. But for the majority of this course, I'll be using
esa es puramente su decisin personal. Pero durante la mayor parte de
NUnit because it has a longer history than MSTest and I
este curso, usar NUnit porque tiene un historial ms largo que MSTest
personally find it a more elegant testing framework.
y personalmente considero que es un marco de prueba ms elegante.
Now, an optional tool that I highly recommend is ReSharper
Ahora, una herramienta opcional que recomiendo es ReSharper porque tiene
because it has a faster and more powerful test runner than the
un corredor de prueba ms rpido y poderoso que el
one built into Visual Studio. Just to let you know,
construido en Visual Studio. Solo para que lo sepan, ReSharper es un
ReSharper is a commercial product, and I'm not their affiliate! You may
producto comercial y no soy su afiliado! Puede decidir comprar una
decide to buy a license or not. That's entirely your choice. What I wanna
licencia o no. Esa es completamente tu eleccin. Lo que quiero
emphasize is that you do not need ReSharper to write or
enfatizar es que no necesita ReSharper para escribir
run tests. But I use ReSharper because it's a
o ejecutar pruebas. Pero uso ReSharper porque es
huge productivity booster. Another optional tool
un gran refuerzo de productividad. Otra herramienta opcional es Rider
is Rider… If you like Visual Studio + ReSharper
Si te gusta Visual Studio + ReSharper pero
but you think Visual Studio is too slow for you, then I highly recommend
crees que Visual Studio es demasiado lento para ti,
you to try Rider. Rider is basically a cross-
te recomiendo que pruebes Rider. Rider es bsicamente un
platform IDE built by JetBrains, the same
IDE multiplataforma construido por JetBrains, la misma compaa
company that has made ReSharper. So you have a super fast
que ha fabricado ReSharper. As que tienes un IDE
IDE+ ReSharper with the exact same shortcuts you use
+ ReSharper sper rpido con los mismos atajos exactos que
in Visual Studio. In this course, I'm gonna record the first few videos
usas en Visual Studio. En este curso, voy a grabar
with Visual Studio because that's the default IDE for
los primeros videos con Visual Studio porque ese es el IDE
the majority of you, but later I'm gonna switch to Rider because that's a lot
predeterminado para la mayora de ustedes, pero ms tarde cambiar a
faster. You can use Visual Studio with or without ReSharper.
Rider porque es mucho ms rpido. Puede usar Visual Studio con o sin ReSharper.
That's perfectly fine. Your focus should be on the fundamentals of writing
Eso est perfectamente bien. Su enfoque debe estar en
good tests, and not the tooling.
los fundamentos de escribir buenas pruebas, y no en las herramientas.